phonedog.com 2013-06-05

# Privacy Policy | PhoneDog

**PhoneDog respects your privacy.**   We have created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our commitment to you, our consumer. This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for this site, phonedog.com.

  * We do not give third parties access to your personal information. 
  * We only send e-mail or postal mail to you if you have elected to receive it, have signed up for a new plan, or to inform you of a new plan or product.

**We will never give any information about you to others without your express permission.**   Our site uses forms in which you give us contact information (like your name, address, and e-mail address) so you can place orders, request information and make suggestions. We use your customer information only when it will be important for us to contact you regarding changes to our service, our Web site and special offers we think you'll find valuable.

However, if you decide to register for a product or service, PhoneDog or the company you select will ask you for any relevant information needed to process your order. All this is done through a secure site provided by PhoneDog or the selected merchant. All of these companies have strict privacy policies that only use your information for the sole purpose of providing you service. See each company’s privacy policies for more details.

 We use information gathered about you from our site statistics (for example, your IP address) to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. We also gather broad demographic information from this data to help us improve our site and make your browsing and purchasing experience more enjoyable. This is not linked to any personally identifiable information. Our site uses cookies to keep track of your site visit. We use cookies to track the amount of traffic we receive and troubleshoot any browser issues. This site may also contain links to other sites. Unfortunately, PhoneDog is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

**Advertising Networks**  
We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web Site. If so, a list of these ad serving companies will be available here. These companies may use information (generally, not including your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number) about your visits to this Web Site and to other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. These companies may employ cookies and clear GIFs to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and clear GIFs is generally not personally identifiable (unless, for example, you provide personally identifiable information to them through an ad or e-mail message). We encourage you to read these businesses' privacy policies if you should have any concerns about how they will care for your personal information. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, see the Network Advertising Initiative's consumer web site at http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.

  * Google: <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>
  * Netshelter: <http://www.netshelter.net/privacy>
  * Kontera: <http://www.kontera.com/kontera-privacy-policy>

**Behavioral Advertising Opt-out  
** You may opt-out of behavioral advertising from any of our associated advertising networks and others by using the NAI Opt-out tool located at: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

**Security**  
This site has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.

**Sending E-mails**  
We use e-mails to communicate with you, to confirm your placed orders, and to send information that you have requested. We also provide e-mail links, as on our "Ask A Question" page, to allow you to contact us directly. We strive to reply promptly to your messages.

The information you send to us may be stored and used to improve this site and our products, or it may be reviewed and discarded. However, your information will only be shared with third parties with your explicit permission.

**Only If We Have To**  
As stated previously in this policy, we will never give out your information without your permission, except when you sign up for a new long distance or local plan. This information will also be needed by your new long distance carrier for the purpose of receiving service from the new company.

The only other exceptions to this are when we are required by law in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law, or we must comply with a legal process served on our Web site.

**Contest**  
From time to time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address) and demographic information (such as zip code and age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used to monitor or improve the use and satisfaction of this site.

**Contacting the Web Site**  
If you have any questions about our privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, contact...

Thank you for your support.
